#### Tom A Steinman

IT professional with over 12 years of experience in customer support, system development, and project management. As a Computer Science major proficient in Python, Java, C++, and AGILE/SCRUM processes, I'm seeking software engineering positions that complement my ongoing bachelor's degree studies that offer the opportunity for full-time employment at graduation. Obtains an active US Secret clearance.

## **Areas of Expertise**

- Python, C++, Java, Qt, unit testing
- Runtime Efficiency- Big O, Omega, Theta
- Data structures and algorithms
- Windows 2000/XP/7/8/10/11

### **Professional Experience**

# NSF REU AI-Cybersecurity Research | Kansas City, MO

Intern (06/2024 - Current)

- Research the current trends of research in AI and Cybersecurity
- Implement a research project incorporating AI, cybersecurity and quantum computing
- Present results weekly leading up to a final presentation to high school students

### Broadleaf Inc / ASRC Federal | Manassas, VA

Lead Technician (02/2018 - 03/2020, 09/2021 - Current)

- Manage the relocation, installation, de-installation, and repair of computers, servers, switches, networking, patching and audio/visual devices
- Supervise up to 24 temporary and part-time employees
- Collaboration with Network Engineers and government employees as an on-site contact, assisting with programming and reconfiguring switches
- Maintaining security and confidentiality adhering to US Secret clearance

### Reliasource | Baltimore, MD

Lead Technician / Field Engineer (07/2010 - 03/2020, 6/2022 - 5/2024)

## Education

Oak Park High School | Kansas City, MO College Preparatory Degree

University of Missouri-Kansas City | BA in Computer Science | Expected Graduation: 12/2024

Honors Student | 4.0 GPA

## **Github Repository**

https://github.com/tasn78?tab=repositories

### **Education in progress**

C# .Net, SQL, Front-end software engineering, HTML, and Blazor